Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
=The Demon=
=الشيطان=
=Episode 21=
=الحلقة 21=
Dear.
عزيزي.
What did you call me?
ماذا ناديتني؟
Where did you
أين كنت؟
learn that from?
تعلم ذلك من؟
I saw those ladies
لقد رأيت هؤلاء السيدات
calling the men
نداء الرجال
walking next to them.
المشي بجانبهم.
Did I make a mistake?
هل ارتكبت خطأ؟
♪Yet it leaves wounds on me♪
♪ومع ذلك فإنه يترك الجروح عليّ♪
What's it with you?
ما الأمر معك؟
You don't like that?
ألا يعجبك ذلك؟
I do.
أفعل.
♪Yearning for love feels the longest♪
♪الشوق للحب هو الشعور الأطول♪
I love it,
أنا أحبه،
honey.
عسل.
That's it!
هذا كل شيء!
Those men called those ladies that.
هؤلاء الرجال أطلقوا على هؤلاء السيدات هذا الاسم.
♪In the end, we go our separate ways♪
♪في النهاية، نذهب في طرقنا المنفصلة♪
Look at this!
أنظر إلى هذا!
Doesn't it
أليس كذلك؟
look like me?
هل يشبهني؟
♪How do you measure one's concern?♪
♪كيف تقيس اهتمامك؟♪
It's as adorable as you.
إنها جميلة مثلك.
Really?
حقًا؟
I'll take this, mister.
سوف آخذ هذا، يا سيدي.
Sure!
بالتأكيد!
♪Who comes with me on my long journey?♪
♪من يأتي معي في رحلتي الطويلة؟♪
I'll have this.
سآخذ هذا.
Thank you, mister.
شكرا لك يا سيدي.
I need to carry it like this.
أحتاج إلى حمله بهذه الطريقة.
♪Where can I rest after picking up the cold branches?♪
♪أين يمكنني أن أستريح بعد التقاط الأغصان الباردة؟♪
It's you?
هل انت؟
Dayao. Dayao.
داياو. داياو.
Help me.
ساعدني.
My mother's taking me home to study.
والدتي تأخذني إلى المنزل للدراسة.
♪In exchange for my weary face♪
♪في مقابل وجهي المتعب♪
Do it, then.
افعلها إذن.
Why run?
لماذا الركض؟
I don't want to study.
لا أريد الدراسة
I just want to practice swordsmanship.
أريد فقط أن أتدرب على المبارزة.
You must study.
يجب عليك الدراسة.
I take back
انا استرجع
all I said.
كل ما قلته.
I myself ever suffered much
لقد عانيت بنفسي كثيرًا
from being uncultured.
من كونها غير مثقف.
Hurry,
عجل،
follow your mother home and study.
اتبع والدتك إلى المنزل وادرس.
Pardon me,
سامحني
Young Madam.
سيدتي الشابة.
It's all right.
كل شيء على ما يرام.
Goodbye, Dayao.
وداعا داياو.
Goodbye.
مع السلامة.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Study well.
ادرس جيدا.
You sure know a lot now.
من المؤكد أنك تعرف الكثير الآن.
Because you've been such a good teacher.
لأنك كنت معلمًا جيدًا.
How lovely.
كم هو جميل.
Take it.
خذها.
This is so beautiful.
هذا جميل جداً.
Slowly.
ببطء.
Granny.
الجدة.
Drop a hint to my husband that he should get me this.
أعطي تلميحًا لزوجي ليشتري لي هذا.
Got it.
فهمتها.
Granny.
الجدة.
Your goods
بضائعك
are so expensive!
غالية الثمن جداً!
I have no interest in them at all.
ليس لدي أي اهتمام بهم على الإطلاق.
Young Madam.
سيدتي الشابة.
A beauty like you deserves these lovely stuff.
جمال مثلك يستحق هذه الأشياء الجميلة.
This hairpin suits you a lot.
هذا دبوس الشعر يناسبك كثيرًا.
Just buy one.
فقط اشتري واحدة.
Does it look good on me?
هل يبدو جيدا علي؟
It does.
إنه كذلك.
Granny.
الجدة.
I'll take this.
سآخذ هذا.
It's for my wife.
إنه لزوجتي.
Keep the change.
احتفظ بالباقي.
Yes.
نعم.
This hairpin is both elegant
دبوس الشعر هذا أنيق للغاية
and elaborate.
ومفصلة.
It looks wonderful on the Young Madam.
يبدو رائعا على السيدة الشابة.
Shen Wangchen.
شين وانغشن.
There's another gift from you!
هناك هدية أخرى منك!
Look,
ينظر،
Shen Wangchen's just given me another present.
لقد أعطاني شين وانجشن للتو هدية أخرى.
Are you happy?
هل انت سعيد؟
You look lovely!
تبدو جميلة!
- Young City Lord!
- سيد المدينة الشاب!
What's happened with him?
ماذا حدث معه؟
Are you all right, Young City Lord?
هل أنت بخير يا سيد المدينة الشاب؟
What's happened, Young City Lord?
ماذا حدث يا سيد المدينة الشاب؟
What's the matter?
ماذا جرى؟
Young City Lord!
سيد المدينة الشاب!
What's this?
ما هذا؟
He was just fine.
لقد كان بخير.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
What's happening?
ماذا يحدث؟
Why did he pass out?
لماذا فقد وعيه؟
Shen Wangchen.
شين وانغشن.
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
I thought of spending more time with you.
فكرت في قضاء المزيد من الوقت معك.
Looks like
يبدو مثل
my wish isn't going to come true.
أمنيتي لن تتحقق
No...
لا...
No way.
مستحيل.
That won't do.
هذا لن يفعل.
Shen Wangchen.
شين وانغشن.
Don't just lie here.
لا تكذب هنا فقط.
Get... Get up.
انهض... انهض.
Get up and tell me about it.
قم وأخبرني عن ذلك.
Tell me
أخبرني
what's happened.
ماذا حدث.
- Chen! - Shen Wangchen!
- تشين! - شين وانغشن!
Mother.
الأم.
I'm all right.
انا بخير.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Shen Wangchen.
شين وانغشن.
What's the matter with you?
ماذا بك؟
Why is this happening?
لماذا يحدث هذا؟
What's really happened?
ماذا حدث حقا؟
Tell me! Tell me!
أخبرني! أخبرني!
You're scaring me, Shen Wangchen!
أنت تخيفني، شين وانغشن!
Get up first, Shen Wangchen!
استيقظ أولاً، شين وانجشين!
Chen!
تشين!
What are you trying to do?
ماذا تحاول أن تفعل؟
Shen Wangchen was aware
كان شين وانغ تشين على علم
that Dayao's presence
هذا حضور داياو
would fasten the erosion of the demon core.
من شأنه أن يعمل على تسريع تآكل جوهر الشيطان.
Why did he insist on doing so?
لماذا أصر على ذلك؟
Si Ming.
سي مينغ.
Fate
قدر
is all destined.
كل شيء مقدر.
This
هذا
is beyond our control.
هو خارج عن سيطرتنا.
Get up first.
استيقظ أولاً.
Tell me about it.
أخبرني عن ذلك.
Today,
اليوم،
you all will meet your demise!
سوف يلقون حتفهم جميعا!
Shang Xin is actually
شانغ شين هو في الواقع
trying to nurture the double demon cores
محاولة رعاية نوى الشيطان المزدوجة
seized from Fan Dayao with the people's primordial spirit!
تم الاستيلاء عليها من فان داياو بروح الشعب البدائية!
Then what are we waiting for?
إذن ماذا ننتظر؟
The demon cores are showing up.
بدأت تظهر نوى الشيطان.
We'll get killed if we make a move now.
سوف نقتل إذا تحركنا الآن.
Shen Wangchen.
شين وانغشن.
You lied to me.
لقد كذبت علي.
You said
أنت قلت
we wouldn't end up like what we had in the past lives.
لن ننتهي كما كان الحال في حياتنا الماضية.
I won't let you die on me.
لن أدعك تموت علي.
Dayao.
مع السلامة.
It's all my destiny.
إنه كل مصيري.
The double demon cores
نوى الشيطان المزدوجة
only appear
تظهر فقط
during a life-and-death moment.
خلال لحظة حياة أو موت.
What?
ماذا؟
Promise me.
وعدني.
Return to Qianchun Mountain
العودة إلى جبل تشيان تشون
and be a good chief.
وكن رئيسًا جيدًا.
Please.
لو سمحت.
I don't want...
أنا لا أريد...
I don't want that, Shen Wangchen!
لا أريد ذلك، شين وانجشين!
I love you.
أحبك.
Shen Wangchen.
شين وانغشن.
I don't want it!
انا لا اريده!
Forget about the demon cores, Shen Wangchen!
انسي نوى الشيطان، شين وانجشين!
I can give up on everything!
أستطيع أن أتخلى عن كل شيء!
I don't want the demon cores!
لا أريد نوى الشيطان!
All I want is you!
كل ما أريده هو أنت!
Shen Wangchen!
شين وانغشن!
Don't leave me!
لا تتركنى!
Get up, Shen Wangchen!
انهض، شين وانغتشين!
Shen Wangchen!
شين وانغشن!
My demon core!
جوهر شيطاني!
♪Where did I lose my direction?♪
♪أين فقدت اتجاهي؟♪
♪Only emptiness is left♪
♪لم يبق سوى الفراغ♪
♪Restless, sleepless, we part ways♪
♪أرق، بلا نوم، افترقنا♪
♪As sorrow slowly grows within♪
♪كما ينمو الحزن ببطء في الداخل♪
♪Tears can't heal, smiles still ache♪
♪الدموع لا يمكن أن تشفى، والابتسامات لا تزال تؤلم♪
♪Because my heart's with you♪
♪لأن قلبي معك♪
♪Your gaze melted the haze♪
♪نظرتك أذابت الضباب♪
♪Waiting so long for your return♪
♪انتظر عودتك لفترة طويلة♪
♪The setting sun reminds me of you♪
♪تذكّرني الشمس الغاربة بك♪
♪If the clear sky is torn by storm and rain one day♪
♪إذا تمزقت السماء الصافية بالعاصفة والمطر يومًا ما♪
♪Tears will flow♪
♪الدموع سوف تتدفق♪
♪I will still wait here with no regrets♪
♪سوف أظل أنتظر هنا دون أي ندم♪
♪Waiting so long for your return♪
♪انتظر عودتك لفترة طويلة♪
♪The setting sun reminds me of you♪
♪تذكّرني الشمس الغاربة بك♪
♪In the amber desert, you turn away with tears in your eyes♪
♪في الصحراء الكهرمانية، تبتعد والدموع في عينيك♪
♪I'll welcome you back in a red dress♪
♪سأرحب بك مرة أخرى في ثوب أحمر♪
♪Waiting forever with no regrets♪
♪الانتظار إلى الأبد دون أي ندم♪